From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight.
Territ on deck, third eye in flight.
Truth gets old, it goes unfold.
D-dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
Slightly awake, can't step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
Slightly awake, can't ston't look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
What's up, guys? Who's here? I put some betas right now. Nobody likes me anymore. It's all about
beta. Beta this, beta that. I'm so jealous of that witch. I'm just kidding. I really don't care
less. I mean, fuck. So we'll make a bigger deal out of me than some Persian witch wants to make a
Anyway, I mean it's more jagged the box delivered
What's up guys?
Why everyone's be mad. I mean you got me you got me. I don't know. I don't even got me
No one gets me
Go skits me
That guy I like
Everyone else wants to make a joke at me
Give me a
You know what? He's so warm.
You know my little worm? He's so warm.
Guys, look at, look at,
can't put a heating on the screen.
He's like the sun.
My little sun.
My sun.
That's okay. I'm a joke.
No, no, no.
She's officially made me a joke.
I'm just like some, like, idiot.
I have no, no value.
Just like nobody.
I just like some like fly that she swatted one day. I certainly got some attention
Seriously, why does she have to be so mean like I still mean about it like me put on me
So good. I love you. I have jack in the I like some tacos of cheeseburger
The coffee from a jacket of box
It's okay though. No, it's okay. Okay. I don't care what I am. I just care that I like Mickey guys laugh
When Emma threw me away
Hi, hey, what's up?
Hi, how are you tonight? I'm fine
What happened to me earlier? I think I'm I'm not sure my phone I did or whatever, but I told you guys that I'll be right back
I was getting my clothes out the dryer
Sorry, I ended for a little bit and then I came back on I just came back on now. How are you doing?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to cut you off at all. No, you're fine. You guys are fine. It's just that um
was answering questions that was from the chat and the guy here he was asking me
like why are you answering questions about God and what I've said was I said
God is a jealous God you know we should always fear him and it's kind of like
the end of I didn't get upset or whatever but yeah yeah
I hear you on that like uh, yeah, I'm sorry. It's hard to get through all my shows sometimes. It's like a little bit
It's a little bit a crazy show
Yeah, this is some drama
But uh, yeah, I want you to get your point across then I don't know how religious you are whatever. Oh, hold on
I'm gonna give you my cat a little
little
Get some
Even a little comb right now. Did you see him combing him?
This is tricks for you. Oh, sorry. No, I'll show you tricks. This is tricks. Oh
Yeah, but um
wouldn't say I'm religious um religious being religious and all that shit you
know um as of present day you know those are just titles you know those those
titles don't mean shit you know you know it's more within than anything right
yeah so right it's here everyone has their own personal relationship with the
You know
Yeah, they asked me they were like
Do you believe in Jesus? And I said no, I don't believe in Jesus. I know Jesus because what I meant was you know, um
They didn't let me finish but
The reason why I said I don't believe in Jesus. I know him because
Within belief, there's doubt, right?
Right, you know the context of big words. How do you get big words by smaller words?
You know, so therefore when you spell believe be L I E
V E right so in between that the suffix within that suffix is lie
So that would be equivalent to like, um, sending him for like doubt, you know, not trusting,
you know, unsure, you know, shit like that.
So when you're knowledgeable to something, those are your facts, right?
Well, that's why I said, I know Jesus, you know, and I'm still, I'm still getting to
know him, you know.
Right well you say when they you say something about like, you know, if you have belief that that implies the kind of doubt
So if you have the total faith, yes, there's like yeah, right absolutely you got it
Yeah, I don't know what you're saying because I have that too
It was like, you know, if you just believe something because you want to believe it and there's like this
So the same amount of doubt because there's like a same thing in a big knowing again
I got like I just a knowing about something and so that's like
Right
It's not so great you can tell and
Yeah, I just have I have some jack-in-the-box coming. I have like a couple of tacos ultimate cheeseburger or whatever
It's like the jack-in-the-box cheeseburger is and a coffee
large coffee and so I've a little bit left a
Little bit steam left to me tonight. So anyone else wants to come on the panel. They're welcome up. We're talking to respectfully and
They're a great guest. Hey Brooke. How are you? We just see everybody over there was doing good
I don't know like beat is like all mad at me today
Like it's been coming on all angry and not like one like nice
Aspects to like reach on to it and say hey, what's up? You know, this is they all mean like every like single communication
Has been negative every single word has been mean like not like what nice word not not one nice word
You know
You know our frequencies and our energies
You know, they pick up on a lot of things, even the things that we are not, you know, conscious of at that moment, you know what I'm saying?
So, we have to be aware of what type of energy is coming around us, whether it's, you know, physical, in a physical sense, you know, personal, or, you know, even online and stuff, you know?
You have to be aware of those things because, you know, you know what Isaac Newton's law is?
Yeah, well, there's gravity like they know there's as a new yeah
Energy never dies whatsoever. It's not yeah whatsoever. So it only transfers
So people are able to transfer their energy to others and stuff no matter if it's good or bad
Well, I know guys, you know beat is live right now
You could you go to be this channel and just say hi be that because you know, I'm apparently nothing and but I have no value
I'm just some idiot. I don't know. She's like basically
Created me she can destroy me and so I'm of no value anymore
So just go to beat his channel and say hi to her and it's like, you know, I'm just like nobody and nothing
I've brought no value to the community. I'm just a bad person
And are you telling me that?
No, I'm telling everybody that.
I'm telling everybody just like, unsubscribe to me
and like, you know, just forget about me.
I'm nothing apparently and I'm nobody.
You're cool.
Why do you feel like that?
No, this is what I've been told all day
by people I care about.
And so it's like,
I don't feel that way about you at all.
Well, thank you.
Let's say if my best friend thinks that then what really what do I care about I say I want it more than you know
More than you know, why do you think you know, this is not my first time being on your live today?
Why do you think you attract so much? You know so many people you're cool dude seriously
It's probably just because I was on some other channel and everyone came over here and like that's not a reason
Well, that's not why I came I I come every now and then sometimes I'll just be in like when I get off of work and stuff
And you know, I'd clean up my house and chill in bed my cat and stuff take a shower
Like laying down chilling. I'll just get on your live and just you know, listen to you speak sometimes seriously
Thank you. Seriously, you're a nice person. You're a nice person and
Like I'm I don't ask for anything either. I just want to like
You know
It's just like have a place here. Hold on a second. Yeah, I'm gonna take it off
Yeah, oh
No, I'm good. I'm good. I
Fixed it
Yeah, if anybody else wants to come on panel though, you're welcome off of handle
I'm just waiting for my jacket the box and then all these my tacos and I eat my burger
But I just go to sleep psych what up may I ask you a question, please? Yeah, of course
Who do you do?
are you are you like religious or whatever yeah and i believe in like the most high god is like
whatever your highest conception of reality like i believe in the highest and then right but i believe
like or like yeah or like kind of stuck in between like the highest and lowest and like
We're like we can choose either way to go to either one
And it's like it's not necessarily either one is like bad or
Like that, but it's like we can like stay in the earthly we can go to the more spiritual
We can like kind of stay in between earth like a spiritual. That's what I am. I'm just gonna like
Do you believe in okay?
So do you believe in spirits and shit like that? Yeah. Yeah
I believe anybody like really dies. I think like we're all like
Yeah
I've come in contact with spirits a lot growing up and
Like the shit is scary seriously
It can be it can be because if you're not like ready to talk to like a past love one and you actually like hear from them
it's like
In like a real way it can be scary because it's like we don't we're conditioned not to believe in this
unknown like
Okay
Something that you're unsure of
um
Oh god
See I get like a little hesitant talking about it or whatever
It happened. Um
To like last year of february
And um, it was so freaking it was so fucking wicked dude. It was so wicked. I wish I can I actually got it
I got a picture of it
Um, yeah, I'm serious. I'm kidding. I'm fucking serious
So like a evil entity?
It was something God forbid that it was evil, but it was here in my house
This was last year in February and it wasn't it didn't happen at night. It happened in the daytime
Mm-hmm. It presented itself in the fucking daytime seriously
Is there um, I wish I could send you the shoes you can put it you can put it on there like as your profile picture
If you want to you have to go backstage and do it like it'll take a second
Hey, yeah, you can do that
Or you can just like tell us your channel and put on your channel or something like that, you know, it's like but uh
Whatever you feel comfortable with I want it. I would like to um
Do you have like a what do you call that shit? Um?
What's at number some shit?
What's app I can do it like you can do it like am I?
I can put it like a email address back backstage or I have a discord or a galata with just
If you can post post it in the backstage. That's all I can see. I'll be able to see it
I want you to see it and then show it to like the chat
So, you know like tell me what energy you pick up from it like you can see it clear as day
You know, um, I had my best my best friend here with me
While I was um while I was doing her hair and shit
She came over to get her hair done before work or whatever and she waitresses right now
So, you know, she wears all black and stuff or whatever
So I have my cat and stuff and she didn't want any cat hair to get on her uniform
So I put the cat in the living room and I was braiding her hair in in my room
and I kind of like put the door adopt the door a jar like kind of close it a little bit and
It was the thing was like leaning against the fucking door dude seriously
Yeah, that's scary. There's like little things that will happen that are like just noticeable by you and it's like
that's actually paranormal activity and
Oh man
It's fucking crazy. Seriously
Like I just heard I just heard the door. I just heard say at the door. Hold on to go
Oh, shit.
Okay, maybe this wishful thinking.
Hey, there's nothing out there.
Hey, I'm still here.
Hold on one second.
Okay, cool.
Okay, I'm probably good.
I don't know I guess nobody would have come on tonight like I don't know it's been like a little bit
Well, just um, I'll get back on whenever you're here. So it's cool
Are you really saying for a while to the show? Um, yeah every now and then yep
Yeah, like what do you like about this show? It's kind of like an unconventional tarot show
It's like not like a normal. I can't hear you. Is it can you hear me now? Oh, I'll be right with you
Okay, I don't know if I I don't my order went through for this food. Oh, let me just check one more time
Okay, if not, I'll just like pass that once again. Here's my cat Lola. Hold on. Let's see Lola
Lola, you want to go on camera? All right
Hey, everyone's left the room. It seems like no one's to be here. So I'm gonna end this in the lab
There's like five people, but there's Lola. Thank you guys. Have a great night. I'm sorry if it bored you bored you guys
Have a good night guys. This is Lola
Yes, no one's gonna stick around love you guys. Well, thank you so much. It'll be a fun night
It's good